Where are you going this Saturday?
I'm leaving.
Getting away for the night.
No, I'm going, I'm gonna drive down to the Bay Area to go see Big Bang.
how did it
well it was when the new song came out for some reason i looked up
i knew they were going on a world tour but i didn't really know where
i had seen kind of stuff of them starting in Korea
And I just happened to look like, oh, it'd be interesting to see where they're going in the U.S.
And it turned out they're only going to two cities, Oakland and New Jersey, somewhere in New Jersey. I don't know where.
And Oakland's not far from here.
And that's two of the three U.S. dates are in Oakland.
So then it's like, oh, I should go!
So obviously, Jaemyun can't go with me because someone has to watch the kids.
So I thought it was pretty unlikely that I would get to go and find someone.
I didn't want to go by myself.
So trying to find someone to go, you know,
I do have friends who listen to Korean music, but not much.
But anyways, I decided to ask my cousin if she wanted to go.
And I don't know if she knows anything about them, if she's ever heard any of their music. If she's ever listened to Kpop, other than like Kpop demon hunters, maybe. Or, you know, hearing BTS.
I'm sure she teaches middle school. So I'm sure she's heard some.
But anyway, she is going to go with me.
So I'm going to drive down, pick her up.
And then we're going to drive all the way down together with her family.
And then go to the concert and spend the night!
We got tickets that are pretty much in the back, the nosebleed section. Cheapest tickets.
Actually, the cheapest and the tickets I got, I think it was like a $ 10 difference.
Hopefully Amy doesn't mind.
If not, I'll just pay for it.
Because it was a much better view between that $ 10. And I was like, it's just worth getting that better view.
So yeah, so we're, we have a decent view.
It's not like it's on the side or like at a weird or obstructed angle or anything,
but it, they were each 150.
I don't like how the ticket website advertised it.
They made it definitely seem that that was the price for two tickets. Not each ticket, even though I selected, I wanted to get two tickets.
But, but, Compared to what we paid in Korea for tickets,
how many years ago? Six years ago?
I was like, it's decent.
And when am I going to go again? So I got them.
All the tickets now, it's like everyone buys them at once and then sells them, resells it.
So yeah, there were no tickets.
I don't know when they officially went on sale, but it seemed like everything was sold.
At least that's what I understood,
but I don't know for sure.
The concerts had already started in Korea by the time I bought a ticket for Oakland.
How did you come to like Big Bang?
When I first got to Korea, I'd say there was a couple of people in my office who really liked Big Bang.
I feel like Fantastic Baby.
I don't know what year that came out,
but... it was still pretty popular like playing Like, you'd hear it on the radio or places were playing it a lot.
So I feel like somehow through that, I started to like it a lot and listening to it.
And then when we met, I feel like you had told me stories of, like, you dancing to it in Hong Kong and stuff like that. I don't know.
And then it just, it was fun groups,
and when they had their last concert in korea before going into the military service we went and got tickets and went
and you got really mad at me for spending so much money
how much was it? it was a lot
i think i spent it was probably $500 in total for our two tickets i think
if..  i think it was around there
i think they were like two three hundred each or something
They were also nosebleed seats,
but you had just had surgery a couple weeks, maybe a month before on your knees.
Well, one knee. And
we should have called in advance to say that, but we didn't.
And there was no way you were in a cast up past your knee to your thigh, like all the way down,  were walking with crutches
there was no way you were getting up to those seats and like no way getting down
and it's just a safety thing as well
so they were not happy
but they finally just put us in to one of the handicap seats which ended up having an amazing view
we were very lucky
i should have called ahead of time
but i just didn't even think about it at that time
so...
Yeah, we got good seats for them.
What is your favorite Big Bang song?
I mean, just, like, the normal, like, hits.
Fantastic Baby, Bang Bang Bang are good.
I do like the new one.
The first time I heard it, I didn't love it, but it did grow on me quite a lot.
I don't know the names well enough to give you,
but
I mean, it's not the best timing right now.
I'm a bit stressed
because I have a lot of assignments due Sunday,
but I'm happy to be going with my cousin and spending some time with her and her husband and his family seeing their daughter Hope.
But
I'm sorry you guys can't come with me.
It would be fun to go together.
Like I do wish we could go together
because we went to the last one,
but it's just with the kids.
It's hard.
Enjoy your time with my mom and uncle.